Guide to the Brooklyn Historical Society vertical files ARC.315
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 2: Brooklyn, 1850-2018; 10 Linear Feet in 5 filing cabinet drawers
  - Politics, Government, Legal -- General, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Politics, Government, Legal -- Political Campaign Ephemera, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Population, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Prisons, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Prison Ships, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Religion -- General, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Religion -- Jehovah's Witnesses, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Religion -- Synagogues, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Religion -- Synagogues -- Congregation Beth Elohim, undated (Drawer 6)
  - Schools, Universities, Colleges -- General, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Schools, Universities, Colleges -- Adelphi University, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Schools, Universities, Colleges -- Brooklyn Institute Council, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Schools, Universities, Colleges -- Brooklyn College, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Schools, Universities, Colleges -- East, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Schools, Universities, Colleges -- Industrial School Association, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Schools, Universities, Colleges -- Kingsborough College, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Schools, Universities, Colleges -- Long Island University, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Schools, Universities, Colleges -- Medgar Evers College, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Schools, Universities, Colleges -- Packer Collegiate Institute, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Schools, Universities, Colleges -- Polytechnic University, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Schools, Universities, Colleges -- Pratt Institute, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Schools, Universities, Colleges -- Roosa School of Music, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Schools, Universities, Colleges -- St. Francis College, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Social Life, Lifestyle, Social Customs -- General, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Social Life, Lifestyle, Social Customs -- Bicycles, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Social Services, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Sports -- General, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Streets -- Atlantic Avenue, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Streets -- Atlantic Avenue Tunnel, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Streets -- Bergen Street, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Streets -- Brooklyn Queens Greenway, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Streets -- Brooklyn Queens Expressway, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Streets -- Flatbush Avenue, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Streets -- Washington Avenue, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Theaters, Performance Spaces, Music Halls -- General, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Theaters, Performance Spaces, Music Halls -- Brooklyn Academy of Music, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Theaters, Performance Spaces, Music Halls -- Brooklyn Philharmonic, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Theaters, Performance Spaces, Music Halls -- Loew's Kings, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Theaters, Performance Spaces, Music Halls -- Loew's Oriental, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Theaters, Performance Spaces, Music Halls -- Tilyou Family, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Tourism and City Guides -- Tourism Industry, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Tourism and City Guides -- Guidebooks, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Tourism and City Guides -- Walking Tours, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Transportation -- General, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Transportation -- Elevated Railways, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Transportation -- Ferries, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Transportation -- L.I.R.R., undated (Drawer 7)
  - Transportation -- Metropolitan Transit Authority, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Transportation -- Trolleys, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Urban Studies -- Brooklyn Studies Seminars, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Urban Studies -- Central Brooklyn Model Cities, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Urban Studies -- Civi Improvement, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Urban Studies -- Gentrification, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Urban Studies -- Housing, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Urban Studies -- Urban Development, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Urban Studies -- Urban Planning, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Urban Studies -- Urban Renewal, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Waterfront, undated (Drawer 7)
  - Women, undated (Drawer 7)
- Series 3: Biographical, 1780-1990; 2 Linear Feet in 1 filing cabinet drawer
  - Aldridge, Walter Hull (-1959), 1889-1959 (Drawer 9)
  - Andersen, Albert, F.M. (-1961) (Drawer 9)
  - Baker, Bertram (1888/9-1985) (Drawer 9)
  - Barber, Red (1908-), 1988 (Drawer 9)
  - Bard, James (1815-1897), undated (Drawer 9)
  - Bard, John (1815-1856), 1845-1990 (Drawer 9)
  - Barnes, Djuna, 1995 (Drawer 9)
  - Barr, Amelia Edith H., 1911 (Drawer 9)
  - Barstowe, Edward, A. (1842- ), 1989 (Drawer 9)
  - Beecher Family, 1860-1906 (Drawer 9)
  - Bjarkman, Peter C. (1941-), 1997 (Drawer 9)
  - Bow, Clara (1905-1965), 1991 (Drawer 9)
  - Brath, Peter (1901-1989) (Drawer 9)
  - Byrd, Frederick (1805-1857), 1995 (Drawer 9)
  - Cadman, S(amuel) Parkes, 1926 (Drawer 9)
  - Caltagirone, Marian (1929- ), 1933 (Drawer 9)
  - Chisholm, Shirley (1924-2005), undated (Drawer 9)
  - Cooper, John Walcott (1873-1966), 1982 (Drawer 9)
  - Couney, Martin A. (1860/1870-1950), 1939-1979 (Drawer 9)
  - Crane, Nathalia (1913- ), 1936 (Drawer 9)
  - Culin, Stewart (1853-1929), 1989-1990 (Drawer 9)
  - Dilliard, Maud Esther (1924-1975) (Drawer 9)
  - Dykman, Jackson Annan (1887-1974) (Drawer 9)
  - Fabry, Alois (Jr.) (1912-1986), 2006 (Drawer 9)
  - Falconer, John M., 1881-1975 (Drawer 9)
  - Fedde, Elisabeth (Sister) (1850-1921), undated (Drawer 9)
  - Fehrer, Oscar (1872-1958), undated (Drawer 9)
  - Felt, David (1793- ), 1989 (Drawer 9)
  - Ferguson, Max (1959- ), 1990 (Drawer 9)
  - Fisher, Ken, 1991 (Drawer 9)
  - Ford, Gordon Lester (1823-1891), 1970 (Drawer 9)
  - Francis, Virginia Fuller, undated (Drawer 9)
  - Freeman, Frank (1861-1949), 1995 (Drawer 9)
  - Furman, Charles, 1899-1953 (Drawer 9)
  - Furman, Gabriel (1800-1854), 1978 (Drawer 9)
  - Gleason, Jackie (1916-1987) (Drawer 9)
  - Green, Anna Katherine (1846- ), undated (Drawer 9)
  - Green, Roger L., 1989-1992 (Drawer 9)
  - Green, William B., 1893-1894 (Drawer 9)
  - Crane, Hart, undated (Drawer 9)
  - Harrigan, Edward (Ned) (1844-1911), 1980 (Drawer 9)
  - Higgins, Charles Michael, 1977-1978 (Drawer 9)
  - Homes, J. Wheldon, 1996 (Drawer 9)
  - Hynes, Charles J. (1935- ), 1980-1996 (Drawer 9)
  - Jolson, Al, undated (Drawer 9)
  - Jordan, MacNeil, undated (Drawer 9)
  - Kelly, James A. (1885-1972), 1944-1977 (Drawer 9)
  - Kroll, Ernest, 1990 (Drawer 9)
  - Lachman, Seymour (1933- ), 1996 (Drawer 9)
  - Lichtenstein, Harvey (1929- ), 1993 (Drawer 9)
  - Lifshey, Samuel H. ( -1954), 1911-1954 (Drawer 9)
  - Loomis, Harvey Worthington (1865-1930), 1930-1990 (Drawer 9)
  - Madden, John B, (1919-1988) (Drawer 9)
  - Manbeck, John B, 1993 (Drawer 9)
  - Marlor, Clark S. (1922- ), 1993 (Drawer 9)
  - Matthews, William (1822-1896), 1892-1896 (Drawer 9)
  - Maynard, Joan (d.2006), 1979 (Drawer 9)
  - McLean, Samuel, undated (Drawer 9)
  - Meadows, Audrey ( -1966), 1996 (Drawer 9)
  - Melish, John Howard ( -1969), 1969-1990 (Drawer 9)
  - Metz, Bill, 1940 (Drawer 9)
  - Montgomery, Velmanette, 1989-1992 (Drawer 9)
  - Moore, Mary Tyler (1936- ), 1996 (Drawer 9)
  - Morris, Montrose W. (1861-1916) (Drawer 9)
  - Moses, Robert, 1975-1976 (Drawer 9)
  - Munson, Audrey, 1913-1920 (Drawer 9)
  - Murphy, Henry Cruse (1810--1882), 1986 (Drawer 9)
  - Nissen, Ludwig (1855-1924), undated (Drawer 9)
  - Ockey, Victor (1943-1988), 1987-1988 (Drawer 9)
  - Othmer, Donald F. (1904-1995), 1978-1995 (Drawer 9)
  - Owens, Major (1936- ), 1991 (Drawer 9)
  - Pantano, Nino, 1974-1977 (Drawer 9)
  - Papp, Joseph (1921-1991) (Drawer 9)
  - Parker, Edgard Rudolph (1872-1952), 1986 (Drawer 9)
  - Patterson, David J., undated (Drawer 9)
  - Paull, Edward T. ( -1924), 1988 (Drawer 9)
  - Peace, Harvey W. (1830-1907), 1993 (Drawer 9)
  - Pennell, Joseph (1857-1926) (Drawer 9)
  - Perkins, Elizabeth Talbot (1866-1956), 2009 (Drawer 9)
  - Pinkett, Mary, 1989-1992 (Drawer 9)
  - Pope, Abbie Hanscom, 1984 (Drawer 9)
  - Ransom, Theodore Sedgwick, 1864-1881 (Drawer 9)
  - Read, Helen Appleton, 1967-1973 (Drawer 9)
  - Reynolds, William H., 1931-1994 (Drawer 9)
  - Robinson, Jackie (1919-1972), 1997 (Drawer 9)
  - Roebling, Emily Warren, 1983-1996 (Drawer 9)
  - Roebling, Washington Augustus, 1988-1994 (Drawer 9)
  - Rosten, Norman (1914-1995), 1979-1995 (Drawer 9)
  - Ryan, Jom, 1990 (Drawer 9)
  - Sanford, Joseph (1797-1831), 1872-1972 (Drawer 9)
  - Schlech, Walter F. (1915- ), 1924-1969 (Drawer 9)
  - Schneerson, Menachem, 1992 (Drawer 9)
  - Secor, John Alstyne, 1980 (Drawer 9)
  - See, Alonzo Bertram (1848-1941), 1995 (Drawer 9)
  - Seidl, Anton (1850-1898), 1991 (Drawer 9)
  - Selby, Hubert (Jr.) (1928- ), 1990 (Drawer 9)
  - Shellens, Michael (1854-1944), 2006 (Drawer 9)
  - Shellens, Ruth M. (1905-1988), 1987-1988 (Drawer 9)
  - Sito, Tom, 1988 (Drawer 9)
  - Sliwa, Curtis, 1970-1980 (Drawer 9)
  - Sliwa, Fran, 1988 (Drawer 9)
  - Smith, Betty (1896-1972) (Drawer 9)
  - Smith, Cyrus Porter ( -1877), 1932 (Drawer 9)
  - Soligny, Eugene Julius, 1990 (Drawer 9)
  - Srebnik, Craig, undated (Drawer 9)
  - Steward, Susan Smith McKinney (1847- ), 1983 (Drawer 9)
  - Stillman, Thomas E. (1826-1906) (Drawer 9)
  - Storrs, Richard Salter, 1880-1896 (Drawer 9)
  - Stryker-Rodda, Kenn (1903-1990) (Drawer 9)
  - Tanzman, Roslyn, 1994 (Drawer 9)
  - Toedteberg, Emma (1824-1909), 1936 (Drawer 9)
  - Towns, Edolphus (1934- ), 1988 (Drawer 9)
  - Trask, Katrina (1853-1922) (Drawer 9)
  - Turnbull, Charles, 1780-1791 (Drawer 9)
  - Van Brunt, James Ryder (1820-1916), 1845-1965 (Drawer 9)
  - Vaux, Calvert (1824-1895), undated (Drawer 9)
  - Vincent, Paul, 1975 (Drawer 9)
  - Volkmar, Charles, 1900 (Drawer 9)
  - Wengenroth, Stow (1906-1978), undated (Drawer 9)
  - White, Alfred T. (1846-1921), 1989-1993 (Drawer 9)
  - Whitman, Walt (1819-1892), 1846-1995 (Drawer 9)
  - Willensky, Elliot ( -1990) (Drawer 9)
  - Woodhull, Nathaniel (1722-1776), undated (Drawer 9)